The path of Francesca Johnson's future seems destined
due to an unexpected fork in the road...
The Bridges of Madison County is a drama, romance
film directed by Clint Eastwood.
Photographer Robert Kincaid wanders into the life of housewife
Francesca Johnson for four days in the 1960s.
Francesca Johnson, played by Meryl Streep.
Robert Kincaid, played by Clint Eastwood.
Caroline Johnson, played by Annie Corley.
Michael Johnson, played by Victor Slezak.
Richard Johnson, played by Jim Haynie.
Young Carolyn, played by Sarah Zahn.
The Bridges of Madison County is a 1995 American romantic drama film based on the
1992 bestselling novel of the same name by Robert James Waller.
It was produced and directed by Clint Eastwood, who also
starred in the film alongside Meryl Streep.
The screenplay was adapted by Richard LaGravenese.
Kathleen Kennedy was co-producer.
It was produced by Amblin Entertainment and Malpaso
Productions, and distributed by Warner Bros.
Entertainment.
The Bridges of Madison County is set in 1965 and features Italian war bride Francesca Johnson
(Meryl Streep), who lives with her husband and two children on their Iowa farm.
That year she meets National Geographic photojournalist Robert Kincaid (Clint Eastwood), who
comes to Madison County, Iowa to photograph its historic covered bridges.
With Francesca's family away for a short trip, the couple
have an intense, four-day love affair.
The film was released on 2 June 1995 and earned $182 million worldwide.
It received generally positive reviews upon release, with high praise directed towards Streep's performance,
earning her a nomination for the Academy Award for Best Actress at the 68th Academy Awards.
The film explores themes of adultery, secret love, husband wife
relationship, based on novel or book, love of one's life.
The tone is emotional.